☰

✕

Terms and Conditions & Privacy Policy
=====================================

Welcome to our website!  
By accessing and using this website, you agree to comply with and be bound by the following Terms and Conditions of Use, as well as our Privacy Policy. If you disagree with any part of these terms, please do not use this website.

The terms '[HTML-Online](https://html-online.com/),' 'us,' or 'we' refer to the owner of the website. The term 'you' refers to the user or viewer of our website.

Privacy Policy
--------------

**Data Collection:** This website does not directly collect or store personal data. However, third-party tools and services used on this website may collect personal information. These include:

* Google Analytics
* Google AdSense
* SetupAds
* Google Mail
* Facebook social widgets
* Cloudflare CDN
* Hosting services: GoDaddy, Bluehost, SiteGround

Please refer to the privacy policies of these third parties for details about their data collection and processing practices.

The [**Online HTML Editor**](https://html-online.com/) works on the client-side and it never sends your text to our server.

**Cookies:** We use cookies to enhance your experience on this website. Cookies may be used for the following purposes:

* Collecting anonymous visitor statistics via Google Analytics
* Displaying personalized ads via Google AdSense
* Saving editor settings
* Identifying first-time visitors

By continuing to use this website, you consent to the use of cookies. You can manage or disable cookies in your browser settings. For more details, please review the privacy policies of Google Analytics and Google AdSense.

**Your Rights:** Under GDPR, you have the following rights regarding your personal data:

* The right to access any personal data collected by third-party services.
* The right to rectify inaccurate or incomplete data.
* The right to request erasure of your data (right to be forgotten).
* The right to restrict or object to data processing.
* The right to data portability.
* The right to withdraw consent for data processing at any time.
* The right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority.

To exercise these rights for data collected by third-party services, please contact the relevant third-party provider directly.

Terms of Use
------------

By using this website, you agree to the following terms:

* The content of this website is for general information and use only. It is subject to change without notice.
* We do not guarantee the accuracy, timeliness, performance, completeness, or suitability of the information and materials provided. You acknowledge that such information may contain inaccuracies, and we expressly exclude liability to the fullest extent permitted by law.
* Your use of any information or materials on this website is at your own risk. It is your responsibility to ensure that any services or information meet your specific requirements.
* The content on this website, including scripts, design, layout, appearance, and graphics, is owned by or licensed to us. Unauthorized reproduction is prohibited unless expressly permitted in our copyright notice.
* All trademarks reproduced on this website that are not owned by or licensed to us are acknowledged on the website.
* Unauthorized use of this website may result in a claim for damages and/or criminal prosecution.
* This website may include links to external websites for your convenience. These links do not imply endorsement, and we are not responsible for the content of linked websites.
* Your use of this website and any disputes arising from such use are governed by the laws of England, Northern Ireland, Scotland, and Wales.

Contact Information
-------------------

If you have any questions about these Terms and Conditions or the Privacy Policy, [please contact us](https://html-online.com/articles/author/contact/).

Latest update: December 11, 2024

This website is using cookies to provide a better user experience.  
You can adjust your browser settings or stop using this website.

© HTML Online [Privacy, Terms and Conditions](https://html-online.com/privacy-terms-and-conditions/)
